A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.9-RG 1.15 (A83-A89) FA479
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 83), 1961-1991; bulk; 1.9; 145.2 Cubic Feet; 121 standard record storage boxes - Boxes R1990-R2070, R2002A, R2002B, R2002C, R2002D, R2044A, R2076-R2110.
  - Utilization of Fragile Environments and Marginal Lands, 190
    - New Mexico State University - Sudano-Sahelian Region (Box R2034)
  - 195
    - National Institute of Nutrition - Ponce de León, 1979-1982 (Box R2034)
    - Pan American Health Organization: - Infectious Diseases, 1980-1983 (Box R2034)
  - United States, 200
    - Alcorn A & M College - Rural Development, 1968-1978 1980 1982 (Box R2034)
    - Rural Development (suppl. - material) (Box R2035)
    - Aspen Institute - AFRICAN Refugee Conference, 1980-1982 (Box R2035)
    - Atlanta University - Administrator-in-residence, 1978-1981 (Box R2035)
    - Atlanta University - Educational - Administration - Ph. I. Program, 1973 1975-1983 (Box R2035)
    - Atlanta University - Educational - Administration - Ph. I. Program (suppl. material) (Box R2036)
    - Atlanta University Center - Fellows & Interns Program, 1976-1981 (Box R2036)
    - Bass, Jack, 1979-1981 (Box R2036)
    - Bolden Decision Impact - Conference, 1980-1982 (Box R2036)
    - Chicago Common Association - Latin Communities, 1971-1982 (Box R2037)
    - Clark College - Economic Policy & Black Americans, 1980-1982 (Box R2037)
    - Clemson University - Rural Cooperatives, 1972 1975-1978 (Box R2038)
    - Columbia University - Italy in the 1970's Conference, 1978 (Box R2038)
    - Community Renewal Society - Race Relations Reporting, 1971 (Box R2039)
    - Conference Board - Economic Policy Conference, 1981 (Box R2039)
    - Cornell University - Biota (Box R2039)
    - Cornell University - Breast Feeding Study, 1978-1982
    - Cornell University - Minority Graduate Students Research, 1977-1981 (Box R2040)
    - Earthwatch Expeditions, Inc. - Educational Impact, 1980-1982 (Box R2040)
    - George Washington University - Educational Policy Fellowships, 1974-1981 (Box R2041)
    - Indochina Refugee Action Center - Cambodia Crisis Center, 1979-1981 (Box R2041)
    - Institute for Education Leadership - Power Guide, 1981-1982 (Box R2041)
    - Institute for Policy & Management Research - Inflation and Deprivation, 1979-1981 (Box R2041)
    - International Fertilizer Development Center - Ashby, 1978-198[?] (Box R2042)
    - Iowa State University - Forest Resource Management, 1975-198[?] (Box R2042)
    - Macalester College - Native American Community Involvement, 1974-198[?] (Box R2042)
    - Michigan State University - Delaware Desegregation, 1976-198[?] (Box R2042)
    - Michigan State University - Delaware Desegregation (suppl. material) (Box R2043)
    - NAACP - Lexis (Box R2043)
    - National Conference of Black Lawyers - Career Survey, 1979-19[?] (Box R2043)
    - Newark - Education - Leadership Development, 1973-1978 1982 (Box R2043)
    - Organization for Business Education & Community Advancement Women & Corporate Boards, 1980-1982 (Box R2044)
    - Oxfam America - Exchange Report, 1980-1982 (Box R2044)
    - Public School Desegregation - Conference, 1980-1982 (Box R2044)
    - Papers for Equal Opportunity workshop on affirmative action (Box R2044A)
    - Siam Institute for Mathematics & Society - Environmental Health Factors, 1975-1981 (Box R2044)
    - Siam Institute for Mathematics & Society - Environmental Health Factors & Eval. & suppl. material, 1974
    - Southern Education Foundation - Black Americans in Higher Education Conference, 1981 (Box R2046)
    - State University of New York at Stony Brook - Chesapeake Bay, 1976-1980 (Box R2046)
    - Support Services Alliance, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box R2046)
    - Support Services Alliance, Inc., 1976-1979 (Box R2047)
    - United Negro College Fund, Inc., 1979-1981 1983 (Box R2047)
    - University of California - Educational Leadership, 1977-1981 (Box R2047)
    - University of Chicago - Domestic Urban Policy, 1978-1981 (Box R2047)
    - University of North Carolina - Beach, 1976-1981 (Box R2048)
    - University of North Carolina - Noise Exposure, 1975-1981 (Box R2048)
    - University of Wisconsin - Design and Management, 1976-1981 (Box R2048)
    - Urban Institute - Labor Market & Racial Inequality, 1979-1982 (Box R2048)
    - Vera Institute of Justice - Job Path Manual, 1979-1981 (Box R2049)
    - Washington Research Project - Children's Defense Fund (Box R2049)
    - Washington Research Project - Children's Defense Fund, 1972-1983 (Box R2050)
    - Work in America Institute, Inc. - Decade Ahead, 1976-1979 (Box R2050)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, A
      - Columbia University - Lassa Fever, 1976-1981 (Box R2028)
      - Columbia University - Nutrition, 1976-1978 1981 (Box R2028)
      - Cornell University - Communicable Disease Center (in Bahia), 1974-1980 1982 (Box R2028)
      - Expanded Definitions of Health Conference, 1980-1981 (Box R2028)
      - Johns Hopkins University - Health Indicators, 1979-1982 (Box R2028)
      - Johns Hopkins University - Onchocerciasis, 1974-1981 (Box R2029)
      - National Academy of Sciences - Health in the Middle East (Box R2029)
      - National Academy of Sciences - International Health (Box R2029)
      - Rockefeller University - Amebiasis, 1978-1982 (Box R2029)
      - Rockefeller University - Reproductive Biology, 1970-1981 (Box R2030)
      - Rockefeller University - Trypanosomes Drug, 1980-1982 (Box R2030)
      - University of Florida - Nutrition of the Elderly Poor, 1977-1981 (Box R2030)
      - University of Pennsylvania - Mammalian Oogenesis, 1979-1981 (Box R2030)
      - University of South Carolina - Medical Systems, 1979-1982 (Box R2031)
      - Yeshiva University - Fibrotic Liver, 1977-1982 (Box R2031)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Botanical Society of America, 1977-1982 (Box R2051)
      - Kettering Research Laboratory - Nitrogen Fertilizer, 1976-1982 (Box R2051)
      - Montana State University - Insect Control, 1980-1982 (Box R2052)
      - Resources for the Future - Agricultural Production, 1976-1982 (Box R2052)
      - University of California - Potato Blight Conference, Riverside, 1980-1981 (Box R2052)
      - University of Colorado - Plant Protease, 1979-1981 (Box R2052)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Bronner, Simon Joseph, 1976-1981 (Box R2052)
      - Gonzalez, Alicia Maria, 1976-1982 (Box R2052)
      - Lawyer, Arthur Lewis, 1978-1982 (Box R2052)
      - Lipson, Carolyn M., 1975-1982 (Box R2053)
      - Long, Arthur Dennis, 1976-1981 (Box R2053)
      - Mackill, James David, 1977-1982 (Box R2053)
      - Maggard, Sally Ward, 1976-1983 (Box R2053)
      - Nickells, Steven Patrick, 1977-1981 (Box R2053)
      - Smith, Margaret Elizabeth, 1977-1981 (Box R2053)
      - Strickland, John S., 1977-1982 (Box R2053)
      - Williams, John Roger, 1975-1983 (Box R2053)
      - Zodda, Deni Michael, 1979-1981 (Box R2053)
    - United States - Population Sciences, P
      - Boston Family Planning Project, 1981-1983 (Box R2054)
      - Columbia University - Teenage parenting, 1979-1981 (Box R2054)
      - University of Michigan - Fertility in Taiwan, 1979-1982 (Box R2054)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, R
      - African-American Institute, Inc. - African artists, 1977-19[?] (Box R2054)
      - Alliance for the Development of Theatre Arts, 1979-1982 (Box R2054)
      - American Academy of Arts & Sciences - Progress Conference, 1978-1982 (Box R2054)
      - American Association for the International Commission of Jurists - Islamic Law Conference, 1978-1983 (Box R2054)
      - American Historical Association - Public History Fellows, 1979-1981 (Box R2055)
      - American Philosophical Association - International Conference, 1976-[?] (Box R2055)
      - American Place Theatre - Musical Theatre, 1977-1981 (Box R2055)
      - American University - Olmstead papers, 1971-1982 (Box R2055)
      - Ashley, Robert R., 1977-1980 (Box R2055)
      - Atlas Theatre Company, Inc. - International program, 1978-1979 198[?] (Box R2055)
      - Aurora Music Foundation - Opera, 1979-1982 (Box R2055)
      - Avant-Garde Music Festivals, Inc. - Concerts, 1979-1982 (Box R2055)
      - Bay Area Video Coalition, Inc. - "Western Exposure" Ser[unreadable], 1977-1981 (Box R2055)
      - Beck, Stephen, 1976-1983 (Box R2056)
      - Biographical Research Center - Symposium, 1978-1982 (Box R2056)
      - Boston Film/Video Foundation, 1977-1981 (Box R2056)
      - Business Committee for the Arts, Inc. - Marketing for the Arts, 1975-1978 (Box R2056)
      - Carter Family Memorial Music Center, Inc., 1978-1982 (Box R2056)
      - Center for Educational Production - "Los Puertorriquenos", 1978-1982 (Box R2057)
      - Chelsea Theatre, Inc. - International Plays, 1976-1981 (Box R2057)
      - Chicago Editing Center, 1977-1981 (Box R2057)
      - Creative Music Foundation, Inc. - Composers Program, 1977-1982 (Box R2057)
      - Cultural Council Foundation - Artists-in-residence, 1977-1981 (Box R2057)
      - Cultural Council Foundation - Film Documentary, 1978-1981 (Box R2057)
      - Cunningham Dance Foundation, Inc. - England Residency, 1979-1981 (Box R2058)
      - Cunningham Dance Foundation, Inc. - Video Project, 1973 (Box R2058)
      - Davis, Jamie, 1978-1981 (Box R2058)
      - Dean Dance & Music Foundation, Inc., 1978-1983 (Box R2058)
      - DeMott, Benjamin, 1975-1983 (Box R2058)
      - District 1199 Cultural Center - Images of Labor, 1978-1982 (Box R2058)
      - Douglass Creative Arts Center, Inc. - "American Rag" Publication, 1979-1981 1983 (Box R2058)
      - Emory University - Cameron, 1979-1982 (Box R2058)
      - ETRA, WILLIAM, 1976-1979 1981 1983 (Box R2059)
        Date of transfer 9/1/1983
      - EXPLORATION, 1975-1980 (Box R2059)
      - FINK, KENNETH, 1975-1982 (Box R2059)
      - FRIEDMAN, RAYMOND, 1980-1982 (Box R2059)
      - FRY, AMELIA R., 1979-1981 (Box R2059)
      - GEORGE WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY VAN DER ZEE PHOTOGRAPHY BOOK, 1977-1981 1983 (Box R2059)
      - GLOBAL VILLAGE OUR CHILDREN FILM, 1979-1983 (Box R2059)
      - GREEFIELD, AMY, 1979-1981 1983 (Box R2059)
      - GREMP, DAVID, 1978-1982 2004 (Box R2059)
      - HOIBY, LEE, 1979-1981 (Box R2059)
      - HARVARD UNIVERSITY ETHICS AND PUBLIC POLICY, 1977-1982 (Box R2059)
      - IMAGES ARTIST-IN-RESIDENCE, 1977-1980 (Box R2059)
      - English Speaking Union - Television Series, 1980-1982 (Box R2058)
      - Etra, William, 1976-1979 1981 1983 (Box R2059)
      - Exploratorium, 1975-1980 (Box R2059)
      - Fink, Kenneth, 1975-1982 (Box R2059)
      - Friedman, Raymond, 1980-1982 (Box R2059)
      - Fry, Amelia R., 1979-1981 (Box R2059)
      - George Washington University - Van Der Zee Photography Book, 1977-1981 1983 (Box R2059)
      - Global Village - Our Children Film, 1979-1983 (Box R2059)
      - Greenfield, Amy, 1979-1981 1983 (Box R2059)
      - Gremp, David, 1978-1982 (Box R2059)
      - Harvard University - Ethics & Public Policy, 1977-1982 (Box R2059)
      - Hoiby, Lee, 1979-1981 (Box R2059)
      - Images - Artist-in-residence, 1977-1980 (Box R2059)
      - Images - Atlantic Center for the Arts, 1980-1981 (Box R2060)
      - Indiana University - Semiotics (Box R2060)
      - Just Above Midtown, 1975-1978 1980 (Box R2060)
      - Kansas City Art Institute - Video Curriculum, 1973-1981 (Box R2060)
      - KQED - Media Probes, 1976 1978-1981 (Box R2060)
      - Kendrick, John, 1977-1981 (Box R2060)
      - Kineholistics Foundation, Inc. - Clarke, 1977-1982 (Box R2061)
      - Kubota, Shigeko, 1978-1982 (Box R2061)
      - Lindisfarne Association, Inc. - Humanities Institute, 1979-1981 (Box R2061)
      - Long Beach Museum of Art - Video Project, 1974-1982 (Box R2061)
      - Louisiana State University - Television's Vietnam, 1979-198[?] (Box R2062)
      - Macbeth, Robert, 1977-1982 (Box R2062)
      - Magic Theatre, Inc. - New Works, 1977-1982 (Box R2062)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Artists' Fellowships, 1977-19[?] (Box R2062)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Artists' Fellowships (suppl. material) (Box R2063)
      - Naropa Institute - Poetry Programs, 1979-1981 (Box R2063)
      - National Academy of Science - China Visit, 1980-1982 (Box R2063)
      - National Academy of Science - History & Philosophy of Science, 1976-1980 (Box R2064)
      - National Black Touring Circuit, Inc., 1979-1981 (Box R2064)
      - National Council of the Churches - Inter-Religious Dialogues, 1974-1980 (Box R2064)
      - New England Conservatory of Music - American Chamber Music, 1979-1981 (Box R2064)
      - New York Community Trust - Center for Communication, 1980-1982 (Box R2064)
      - New York University - Artists Workshop, 1979-1981 (Box R2064)
      - New York University - Telecommunications, 1976-1982 (Box R2064)
      - North Carolina Dance Theater - Choreographers, 1979-1983 (Box R2065)
      - Oklahoma State University - Television's Vietnam, 1978-1979 (Box R2065)
      - Paperback Television, Inc. - Pilot Program, 1977-1982 (Box R2065)
      - Perspectives International - History of Black America Colleges, 1979-1981 (Box R2065)
      - Raymond, Alan, 1979-1983 (Box R2065)
      - Rodgers Dance Company - New Works, 1978-1983 (Box R2065)
      - San Francisco Video Artists, 1978 (Box R2065)
      - S.E.M. Ensemble - South American Tour, 1978-1981 (Box R2065)
      - Smithsonian Institution - History & Policy Analysis Conference, 1977-1981 (Box R2066)
      - Snyder, Robert, 1978-1982 (Box R2066)
      - Solaris Dance Theater - Indian Dance, 1979-1982 (Box R2066)
      - State University of New York - American Modern Dance Festival, 1980-1982 (Box R2066)
      - Stuart, Martha, 1979-1982 (Box R2066)
      - Theatre Communications Groups - Plays in Progress, 1978-1982 (Box R2066)
      - University of California - Douglas Oral History Project (Box R2066)
      - University of California - Music Center, San Diego, 1968-198[?] (Box R2067)
        - Computer Sound Demo Tape, 1979
          Scope and Contents note
          Tracks from "the serpent-snapping eye" and "Voicespace III: The Palace," by R. Reynolds.
      - University of California - Public History Conference (Box R2068)
      - University of Connecticut - Cities Conference, 1977-1981 (Box R2068)
      - University of La Verne - Padua Hills Writers Workshop, 1979-1981 (Box R2068)
      - University of Maryland - National Boundary Problems, 1979-1981 (Box R2068)
      - University of North Carolina - ACLA, 1979-1982 (Box R2068)
      - University of Pennsylvania - Humanistic Perspective, 1979-1981 (Box R2068)
      - University of Southern California - Authority Conference, 1979-1982 (Box R2068)
      - Urban Communication Group - Rosa Parks Film, 1980-1982 (Box R2068)
      - WGBH Educational Foundation - Roemer, 1978-1982 (Box R2069)
      - WGBH Educational Foundation - Workshop, 1973-1983 (Box R2069)
      - WQED - Media Probes, 1981-1983 (Box R2069)
      - Wayne State University - Black English Conference, 1979-198[?] (Box R2069)
      - Yale University - Media Design, 1974-1983
    - United States - Social Sciences, S
      - Asia Society - China Council, 1975-1976 1979-1980 (Box R2076)
      - Brandeis University - Youth Employment, 1979-1981 (Box R2076)
      - Education Issues - Conference, 1981 (Box R2076)
      - Guttmacher Institute - Abortion Study, 1977-1981 (Box R2076)
      - Harvard University - Indonesian Textbook, 1977-1981 1983 (Box R2076)
      - Kuenne, Robert E., 1976-1981 (Box R2076)
      - League of Women Voters Education Fund - Federal Revenue Sharing, 1979-1981 (Box R2077)
      - National Bureau of Economic Research, Inc. - Economic Analysis of Human Behavior & Social Institute, 1972-1977 1980 (Box R2077)
      - Northwestern University - Male Youth Employment (Box R2077)
      - Puerto Rican Migration Research Consortium - Employment Study, 1976-1982 (Box R2078)
      - Rand Corporation - Fertility & Health Variables, 1972-1983 (Box R2078)
      - Rand Corporation - Fertility & Health Variables (suppl. mat.) (Box R2079)
      - University of Chicago - Food Security, 1979-1982 (Box R2080)
      - University of Pennsylvania - Asian Rice Economy, 1977 1979-[?] (Box R2080)
      - Whiteford, Michael B., 1978-1982 (Box R2080)
    - United States - Schistosomiasis, W
      - New York University, 1978-1982 (Box R2080)
  - Fellowships in Admin, of Early Childhood and Exceptional Children Educational Programs, 267
    - (Fellowships in Admin, of Early Childhood and Exceptional Children Educational Programs - for minority-group educators, 1976-1979 (Box R2090)
    - Fellowships in Admin, of Early Childhood and Exceptional Children Educational Programs - Maryland, 223
      - Cooper, Charlene, 1977-1981 (Box R2090)
    - Fellowships in Admin, of Early Childhood and Exceptional Children Educational Programs - North Carolina, 236
      - Watts, Velma Gibson, 1978-1982 (Box R2090)
    - Fellowships in Admin, of Early Childhood and Exceptional Children Educational Programs - Pennsylvania, 241
      - Brewer, Jeanette W., 1977-1981 (Box R2090)
      - Clayton, Constance E., 1977-1982 (Box R2090)
  - U.S. Education - Administration & Finance Fellowships, 268
    - (U.S. - Education - Admin. & Finance Fellowships), 1974-1982 (Box R2090)
    - U.S. Education - Administration & Finance Fellowships - Fellowships, E
      - Columbia University, 1977-1982 (Box R2090)
      - Isom, Deborah A., 1977-1981 (Box R2090)
      - Lopez, Fidel, 1977-1978 1980-1982 (Box R2090)
  - Equal Opportunity Project in Southern United States, 275
    - Historically Black Colleges, 1979-1981 (Box R2093)
    - Historically Black Colleges - Proposals, 1980-1981 (Box R2093)
    - MRDC (Mississippi Research & Development Center), 1975-1980 (Box R2093)
    - Virginia State College - Community Development, 1975-1982 (Box R2094)
  - Equal Opportunity Projects, 277
    - Columbia University - Urban Labor Markets, 1980-1982 (Box R2094)
    - Manpower Demonstration Research Corp. - Private Sector wage subsidy, 1978 1980-1983
    - National Council on Employment Policy - CETA Program Revision, 1979-1981 (Box R2097)
    - National Opinion Research Center - Youth Unemployment, 197[?] (Box R2097)
  - Training in Museum Education, 280
    - (Training program in Museum Education) (Minutes), 1972-1980 (Box R2098)
    - (Training program in Museum Education) (Minutes), 1972-1979 1981 (Box R2098)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1979-1982 (Box R2098)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art (supp. material) (Box R2099)
    - Walker Art Center, 1970-1979 1981-1982 (Box R2099)
  - Ethnic Archives Development Program, 285
    - (Ethnic Archives Development Program), 1977-1979 (Box R2099)
    - Kent State University - Non-Slavic Archive Cataloging, 1979-1983 (Box R2099)
    - Pilsudski Institute of America - Polish Archive, 1978-1981 (Box R2099)
    - University of Alabama - Ethnic Minority Archives, 1977-1981 (Box R2099)
  - Latin America, 300
    - Latin America - Social Sciences, S
      - Inter-American Institute of Agricultural Sciences - Human Resources, 1977-1981 (Box R2100)
  - Brazil, 305
    - Brazil - Medical Sciences, A
      - Parasite Immunology in Bahia - Conference, 1980-1981 (Box R2100)
    - Brazil - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Congregacao Mariana University - Fishery, 1979-1982 (Box R2100)
    - Brazil - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Almeida, Naomar Monterro De, 1976-1981 1983 (Box R2100)
      - Azevedo, Jose Sergio Gabriello De, 1975-1982 (Box R2100)
      - Lino, Roberto D'Oliveira, 1979-1982 (Box R2100)
    - Brazil - University Develpment, UD
      - University of Bahia - Beans, Wheat and Rice, 1976-1980 (Box R2101)
      - University of Bahia - Oysterculture, 1976-1981 (Box R2101)
  - Colombia, 311
    - Fundacion para la Educacion Superior (FES) - Donation of Equipment, 1977-1978 (Box R2101)
    - Fundacion para la Educacion Superior (FES) - Rural Devel., 1973-198[?] (Box R2101)
    - Fundacion para la Educacion Superior (FES) - Rural Well-being, 1979-198[?] (Box R2101)
    - Colombia - Medical Sciences, A
      - Universidad del Valle - Health Care, 1968-1980 (Box R2101)
      - Universidad del Valle - Health Care, 1968-1980 (Box R2102)
      - Universidad del Valle - Mental Health, 1979-1982 (Box R2102)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Lobo Arias, Mario, 1976-1981 (Box R2102)
  - Mexico, 323
    - Colegio de México - Economic Demography, 1979-1983 (Box R2103)
    - Mexico - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - National School of Agriculture - Rural development Conference, 1980-1981 (Box R2103)
    - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Ortega M., Enrique I. (2nd fellowship), 1977-1980 (Box R2103)
      - Ortiz Ferrara, Guillermo, 1977-1981 (Box R2103)
    - Mexico - Social Sciences, S
      - Colegio de México - International Review Group, 1975-1982 (Box R2103)
      - Colegio de México - International Review Group (suppl. material) (Box R2104)
  - Dominican Republic, 335
    - Dominican Republic - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Asociación para el Desarrollo, Inc. - Development Program, 1977-1981 (Box R2104)
  - Venezuela, 339
    - Venezuelan Federation of Private Foundations - Conference, 1980 (Box R2104)
  - England, 401
    - England - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Hinton, Barry Thomas, 1978-1982 (Box R2104)
    - England - Schistosomiasis, W
      - London School of Hygiene - Data Bank, 1977-1982 (Box R2104)
      - London School of Hygiene - Schistosomiasis Vaccine, 197[?] (Box R2105)
  - Scotland, 405
    - Scotland - Medical Sciences, A
      - University of Edinburgh - Epidemiology Conference, 1980 (Box R2105)
  - Australia, 410
    - Australian National University - African Family Project, 1979-1981 (Box R2105)
  - Canada, 427
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, A
      - Geographic Medicine - Conference, 1980-1981 (Box R2105)
    - Canada - Medical Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - McGill University - Nitrogen Fixation, 1977-1982 (Box R2105)
  - Grenada/Windward Islands, 455
    - Grenada/Windward Islands - Schistosomiasis, W
      - Saint Lucia - Consultants (Davis, A.), 1971-1979 1981 (Box R2105)
      - Saint Lucia - Consultants (Gilles, H.), 1971-1972 1981 (Box R2105)
      - Saint Lucia - Consultants (Mahmoud), 1981 (Box R2105)
      - Saint Lucia - Consultants (Webbe, G.), 1968-1979 1981 (Box R2105)
      - Saint Lucia- Donation of Equipment, 1970-1982 (Box R2105)
  - India, 464
    - India - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - (Agricultural Sciences) - Social Sciences (Gilpatric Chadbourne), 1970-1972 (Box R2105)
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Deolalikar, Anil Bapu, 1980-1981 (Box R2105A)
  - Malaysia, 473
    - Malaysia - Humanities and Arts, R
      - National University of Malaysia - IAHA, 1979-1982 (Box R2105A)
      - National University of Malaysia - IAHA (Suppl. material) (Box R2105A-R2106)
  - France, 500
    - France - Medical Sciences, A
      - Hommel, Marcel, 1978-1981 (Box R2107)
      - Pasteur Institute - Modabber, 1979-1982 (Box R2107)
  - Asia, 600
    - Asia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, D
      - Downy Mildew, 1975-1981 (Box R2107)
  - China, 601
    - China - Fellowships, Scholarships and Training Awards, E
      - Gu, Zhiping, 1979-1981 (Box R2107)
      - Wang Gai Gong, 1979-1982 (Box R2107)
      - Zhuang, Lin-Zh, 1979-1982 (Box R2107)
    - China - Schistosomiasis, W
      - Shanghai First Medical College, 1980-1982 (Box R2107)
  - Japan, 609
    - Tokyo University - Fisheries & Pollution, 1978-1980 1982 (Box R2107)
    - Tokyo University of Mercantile Marine - Shipping Policies in the North Pacific, 1979-1981 (Box R2107)